[{"id": 1451, "question": "When Caleb Forbes got his first job at an advertising company at the age of 20, he thought he would be at the company for years. But after seven months he was bored. Soon after that, Forbes moved to London. He took four different jobs at three companies over the next five years. Forbes wanted a better job and higher pay---he was never quite satisfied. Welcome to the world of a job hopper. Forbes's story isn't unusual these days and such frequent movement from one job to the next will become more common. The main reason: the nature of employment is changing. There are a lot more contracts and part-time jobs or flexible employment. That leads to people having a greater number of jobs. What's more, layoffs and pay freezes , among other things, have pushed people from one job to another. In so...\n\nQ: How did Forbes feel about his first job at first?", "options": ["It was easy.", "It was boring.", "It was satisfying.", "It was dangerous."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1657, "question": "There is an English saying: \"Laughter is best medicine.\" Until recently, few people took the saying seriously. Now, however, doctors have begun to look into laughter and the effects it has on the human body. They have found that laughter really can improve people's health. Tests were carried out to study the effects of laughter on the body. People watched funny films while doctors checked their heart, blood pressure, breathing and muscles. It was found that laughter has similar effects to physical exercises. It increases blood pressure, the heart beating and breathing. It also works several groups of muscles in the face, the stomach, and even the feet. If laughter exercises the body, it must be beneficial. Other tests have shown that laughter appears to be able to reduce the effect of pain...\n\nQ: Doctors hold laughter clinics   _  .", "options": ["to give better condition to their patients", "in order to improve patients' health", "to make patients smile all the time", "to prove smile and laughter have the same effect"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1410, "question": "Amazingly, US crime figures have been falling for 20 years now. Of course, the big question is, why? And can any lessons be learnt? One reason could be the fall in the demand for the drug crack. During the 1980s, drug-related crimes soared, mostly caused by desperate crack users. However, according to professor Blumstein, co-author of The Crime Drop in America, news of the dangers of crack use caused its decrease and led to a fall in the number of drug-related crimes. Some say that the adoption of a zero-tolerance policy in many cities has helped lead to a fall in crime. In New York City, for example, mayor Rudy Giuliani imposed strict and automatic punishments for all crimes, including minor offences such as graffiti and littering. Many believe this has had a very strong deterrent effect....\n\nQ: \"Why Crime Rates Fell\" is mentioned in the article to tell readers that   _  .", "options": ["drug crack can be extremely dangerous", "crime mapping schemes help the police discover criminals", "criminals should be strictly sentenced", "children shouldn't be allowed to contact lead"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 576, "question": "There are three main forms of public transport in Singapore--trains,buses and taxis. TRAINS Trains run from 6:00 am to midnight. Single trip tickets start at 80 cents. If you buy an EZ-Link card for $ 15,you can ride the trains and buses as you like. If you need more infor-mation, just call Train Station at 6222 5165. BUSES There are several bus services in Singapore and fares start at 80 cents. Be sure always to ask the driver the cost of your ticket as he can't give change. If you need help,just call Tran-sit Link at 1800 767 4333. TAXIS There are three main taxi companies--City Cab (6552 2222),Comfort (6552 1111) and Tibs (6552 8888). Booking can also be easy by calling the numbers listed above. RENTAL CARS Driving in Singapore is a pleasure and if you like to travel at your own pace,re...\n\nQ: If you need the bus service? you had better call_.", "options": ["6552 1111", "1800 767 4333", "6552 5165", "+ 65 6737 1668"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3209, "question": "People want action on noise, a recent public meeting in Brisbane showed.Some want technical improvements such as quieter air conditioners or better sound barriers around major roads.Others want tougher laws to restrict noise from building sites or to require owners to take responsibility for barking dogs.But the highest priority was a noise complaints system that works. Brisbane City Council receives more complaints about noise than all other problems put together.So it conducted a survey and found that about half its residents are upset by noise in one form or another -traffic, mowers, pool pumps, air conditioners or loud parties.This inspired the Council to bring together more than 100 citizens one evening to talk through a range of options. The meeting found the present regulatory syste...\n\nQ: How could noise from building sites be alleviated if Brisbane adopted daylight saving?", "options": ["If daylight saving was adopted, the daytime would be prolonged and the night would become quieter.", "If daylight saving was adopted, the working hours during the daytime would be shortened while the night would be extended and thus quieter.", "If daylight saving was adopted, the night would be shortened and thus quieter.", "If daylight saving was adopted, both the daytime and the night would be shortened and the noise would be reduced."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2423, "question": "Millions of girls grow up with the hope of becoming a famous singer. Some even win local talent competitions as children, but only a few such early successes and dreams turn into reality. Jessica Andrews is one of the few whose dreams have come true. Andrews, first taste of success came at the age of 10. She won a talent competition in her home town of Huntingdon, Tennessee, singing I Will Always Love You, originally sung by Whitney Houston. Houston's version of the song appeared on The Bodyguard sound track, which happened to be the first album Andrews ever bought. Within two years, talk of Andrews had spread to Nashville and caught the attention of producer Byron Gallimore, whose credits include work with Tim McGraw, Faith Hill, and Jo Dee Messina. With Gallimore signed on to produce, An...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is WRONG according to the passage?", "options": ["The Bodyguard was the first album Andrews ever bought.", "After Andrews sang Who I Am,she became a star in her own right.", "I Will Always Love You was originally sung by Whitney Houston.", "Now expresses a new feeling of Andrews."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 920, "question": "It's 2035. You have a job, a family and you're about 40 old. Welcome to your future life. Getting ready for work, you pause in front of the mirror, \"Turn red,\" you say. Your shirt changes from sky blue to deep red. Tiny preprogrammed electronics are rearranged in your shirt to change its color. Looking into the mirror, you find it hard to believe that you are 40. You look much younger. With amazing advances in medicine, people in your generation may live to be 150 years old. You're not even middle-aged. As you go into the kitchen and prepare to pour your breakfast cereal into a bowl, you hear: \"To lose weight, you shouldn't eat that,\" from your shoes. They read the tiny electronic code on the cereal box to find out the nutrition details. You decide to listen to your shoes. \"Kitchen, what c...\n\nQ: How do the shoes know that your shouldn't eat the breakfast cereal?", "options": ["By pouring the breakfast into a bowl.", "By listening to the doctor's advice.", "By testing the food supplies in the kitchen.", "By checking the nutrition details of the food."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 340, "question": "John Blanchard stood up from the bench, straightened his Army uniform, and studied the crowd of people making their way through Grand Central Station. He looked for the girl whose heart he knew, but whose face he didn't, the girl with the rose. His interest in her had begun thirteen months before in a Florida library. Taking a book off the shelf he found himself intrigued, not with the words of the book, but with the notes penciled in the margin. The soft handwriting reflected a thoughtful soul and insightful mind. In the front of the book, he discovered the previous owner's name, Miss Hollis Maynell. With time and effort he located her address. She lived in New York City. He wrote her a letter introducing himself and inviting her to correspond. The next day he was shipped overseas for ser...\n\nQ: How could Blanchard recognize Hollis?", "options": ["She would be wearing a rose on her coat.", "She would be holding a book in her hand.", "She would be standing behind a young girl.", "She would be wearing a scarf around her neck."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2722, "question": "Google Works Miracles Google(www.Google.com) is a daily miracle to millions of people. If the Internet had only this very fast search engine, it would have justified its existence many times over. It is the most popular search engine on the web with a 54% market share, ahead of Yahoo! You type almost anything, however unclear, into the space provided and in a second it has come up with hundreds of references. If knowledge is power, then Google commands the gateway. Yahoo Becomes Giant Yahoo(www.yahoo.com) was the first wonder of the web, and in many respects, it still is. It started in January 1994 when two California graduate students, Jerry Yang and David Filo, started compiling a database of links, mainly for their personal use. But well before the end of the year, it had become recogni...\n\nQ: How long did it take for Yahoo to be recognized?", "options": ["One year.", "A month.", "Several years.", "Overnight."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2765, "question": "What is the color1 of the universe? Astronomers had not answered this question until two months ago. That is when two American astronomers reported on their study of all the light in the universe. They said that the universe would appear to the human eyes to be a light greenish color1. Karl Glazebrook and Ivan Baldry of Johns Hopkins University in Baltimore, Maryland, reported their finding in January. They presented the research at a meeting of the American Astronomical Society. They said that finding the color1 of the universe was not part of their more serious scientific research. They did it for fun. However, earlier this month, the scientists admitted making a mistake. They said their finding was much more color1ful than it should have been. They now say the light from our universe is...\n\nQ: Who found the true color1 of the universe?", "options": ["Karl Glazebrook.", "Ivan Baldry.", "Mark Fairchild", "Johns Hopkins.."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 960, "question": "Finally, I entered the university. Because of my careful savings, I did not have to work during the school year. Then, summer came and it was time to work harder than ever. I continued working as a waitress at night, instructed tennis camps several mornings a week and worked as a secretary for a few hours in the afternoons. I even decided to take a class at a community college. This class at the community college saved me $650. It was an extremely tiring summer and made me anxious to return to my relatively easy life at the university. During my second and third years of undergraduate schooling, I decided to work about five hours per week in the campus admissions office answering phones. This provided a little spending money and kept me from drawing my savings out. The overall situation lo...\n\nQ: The writer's major concern about the trip to Israel was that   _  .", "options": ["her mother would not give her approval", "she would fail to get credits in Israel", "a wellpaid summer job would be lost", "$1 600 couldn't be drawn out in time"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3098, "question": "An English saying goes: \" _ \" That means we should relax after a day's hard work or we'll be unhealthy. Many students know that if they want to get ideal jobs with good salaries, they must do well in high school so they can enter good universities. Therefore, they spend all day studying without time to relax. However, not all students can go to top universities even if they work very hard. Students are pressurized by parents and teachers who are just concerned about their studies and exam scores while ignoring their hobbies and individual differences. As a result, students are forces to work harder and harder. Furthermore, there is pressure coming from students themselves. They realize they have a slim chance of getting into a top university as competition is fierce. So, they put a lot of ...\n\nQ: What trouble have both the parents and teachers brought to the students?", "options": ["They don't know how to let the students relax.", "They give too much burden for them to bear.", "They don't love those who work the hardest.", "They fail to understand what the students need most."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2344, "question": "Have you ever intended to be fully absorbed in your work but found yourself distracted by e-mail, the Internet and other things throughout the day? According to the survey made by a famous university in the USA, most people have the experience. \"People often lose their concentration when they are bored, of course, but also when they are engaged in challenging tasks,\" says Peter Bregman, the head of the survey. \"They sometimes have a feeling to escape from what's difficult or boring, so they jump out,\" he says. The part of the brain devoted to attention is connected to the brain's emotional center. Any strong emotion --quarrels with colleagues, problems at home --can interrupt our attention. Studies over the last decade have shown that too much work to do at a time can easily lead to distra...\n\nQ: Which incident might NOT interrupt your attention?", "options": ["You were scolded by your teacher.", "You had words with your good friend.", "You went to school at six as usual.", "Your mother and father had a quarrel."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2908, "question": "When I came to Cincinnati as an au pair , a lot of things there were different from what I knew. My host family lived in a huge house I could only describe as a \"castle\".In Germany I had lived in a small apartment together with my mom. Soon I found out that the \"castle\" was actually rather small in our neighborhood. Everybody there was very friendly and polite. They greeted you when they were walking by at least 3 feet away from you. They must not have seen a German au pair before, for most people I met asked me all kinds of questions about Germany. I enjoyed answering their various strange questions. I made a lot of friends and I started to hang out with them. Of course, there were a number of new things, and it took me the whole year to find them all out. I never got homesick. Perhaps it...\n\nQ: When the author lived in Cincinnati,   _  .", "options": ["she lived in a real castle", "some people were not very kind to her", "many people were curious about her motherland", "she lived in the biggest house in the neighborhood"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 44, "question": "One of the traditions which is now a necessary part of Christmas is a that of Father Christmas, or Santa Claus. According to the modern legend, he is a magical figure who visits all the children of the world during the night before Christmas Day, leaving presents which they find the next morning. He flies through the night sky in a sledge pulled by reindeer, and enters houses by climbing down chimneys. This strange legend is based on the life of a man called Nicholas, but in fact we know very little about him. Historians think he was a Christian bishop in Turkey in about 285--350 A.D. One of the stories about him is that he helped three poor girls. No one would marry them because they were so poor. To provide them with money for their weddings, Nicholas secretly dropped some gold coins dow...\n\nQ: The best title for this passage would be  _  .", "options": ["Is Father Christmas Dangerous?", "The True History of St Nicholas", "The Legend of Santa Claus", "The Traditions of Christmas"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 324, "question": "Now I know that we black people are much more likely to have high blood pressure and diabetes than white people. And _ often lead to heart attacks and other untreated diseases. For example, black people are three to four times more likely than white people to have high blood pressure and twice as likely as the white population to die of a stroke . New research has found out the surprisingly high levels of salt in many of black people's favorite meals. I stopped putting extra salt in my food at the table long ago and I try to cut down on the salt I use in cooking. The recommended daily level of salt for adults is 6 grams. It is easy to see that if you avoid processed foods and use salt in your cooking within the limit, you won't exceed the daily level. The research showed how much salt ther...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Watch the salt.", "Take care, black people.", "Say no to takeaways.", "Say no to high blood pressure."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2187, "question": "Linda and Lucy were best friends. They graduated from high school and went to the same college for further studies. After some days Linda found that her friend was behaving strangely. She would remain quiet, sleep too much and turn wild, very often. At first, Linda thought it was just because of the problems she had met in her studies. However, Lucy became even stranger over time. Finally, Linda couldn't take it any longer and asked Lucy about her strange behavior. Lucy broke into tears and said that she was going around with a boy, who was taking drugs and forcing her to take them, too. Linda was shocked by her story. She then advised her friend to leave the boy. She reminded Lucy of her dreams of becoming a successful doctor and encouraged her to set an example for others. She also remin...\n\nQ: The writer tries to tell us  _  .", "options": ["how we can give up drugs", "how we can overcome difficulty", "how we should help others", "what a true friend is"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3295, "question": "Active vacations are often the most relaxing of all. But Wait! It's all in defining what an active vacation is. We don't expect you to take up jogging, backpacking, or hang gliding. we ask the sedentary vacationers to spend two to four hours a day doing things, such as walking the city streets, exploring a nature preserve, or taking a leisurely rowboat ride. These kinds of activities aren't just good for your physical health. They improve your mental health, even your spiritual health. And they make vacations memorable and worthwhile. Here are some fresh ideas for active and healthy vacation. Make the morning your activity time. At that time it is most likely that the weather will be friendlier, your energy level higher, and your schedule emptier than later in the day. Have a walk at dawn ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is WRONG according to the passage?", "options": ["Usually the weather in the morning is better.", "You can have a memorable vacation in a car.", "Swimming can make you feel much more alive.", "Don't drive your car very often to go sightseeing."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2958, "question": "One morning, a young man leading a goat lost his way due to the thick mist.Then he met a blind man and asked whether he also lost his way.The blind man said, \"I cannot see anything.Therefore, the mist doesn't affect me.I followed the path in my memory and it never goes wrong.\" Happily the young man led the goat following him forward.The blind man asked where he was going.He said he wanted to sell his goat.\"Male or female? How many years have you kept it?\" The young man spoke without too much thought, \"A female goat of 3 years!\" The young man was still following the blind man when he was grasped the hand by the blind man.He shouted ,\"Here is the police station! Go into it and _ on how you stole the goat!\" The young man had been a thief for a long time and admitted the goat was stolen by him...\n\nQ: We can infer that the young man was   _  after hearing the blind man's explanation.", "options": ["humorous", "nervous", "depressed", "satisfied"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2790, "question": "While the other kids seemed excited about celebrating the end-of-term party by playing games and sharing treats, Jeremy hated the very idea of the gathering. Afraid to raise the pressure too high, I decided to contribute something that was easy to purchase on the walk to school. Off we went the day of the party, approaching his school as if nothing was planned. I reminded him of our need to make a purchase, entered his favorite shop, and asked him to select the ripest bunch of grapes. He shot me an anxious look and insisted none of his classmates ever be able to notice he had something to bring to the party. My _ of a successful parenting method, resulting in delivering a sociable child to his school, diverted sharply from reality. Back on route, I did my best to hide the sinking feeling o...\n\nQ: What does the passage mainly talk about?", "options": ["The teacher inspired Jeremy to share grapes.", "Jeremy prepared for the coming party.", "The author helped Jeremy to become sociable.", "The author taught Jeremy to select goods"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1357, "question": "When people get bad toothaches, they often have to eat soft, easily chewed food. When lions get bad toothaches, they eat people? That' s the conclusion of a zoologist at the Field Museum of Natural History in Chicago and a dentist who works on carnivores ., Lions don't normally prey on people. Every once in a while, however, a lion will go on a human-eating diet. The most famous such tragedy happened in 1898, when two lions killed and ate 135 railway workers in prefix = st1 /Kenya. Examining the preserved skulls of the two big cats, zoologist Bruce Patterson and dentist Ellis Neiburger found that both animals had been suffering from several dental and |aw problems. One lion had three missing teeth and a loose, unsteady lower canine that was probably useless. Canines are pointed teeth that ...\n\nQ: The reason why lions don't normally prey on people is   _  .", "options": ["that they like wild preys better", "they just hunt for prey at night,", "that humans are difficult to catch", "not mentioned in the passage"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3072, "question": "In our daily life, many of us feel stressed more or less. Some like this pressure and work better because of it. Others are not comfortable with any stress at alls they soon become unhappy if they feel stressed. Sometimes stress can lead people to do things they wouldn't usually do, such as overeat, smoke, drink, or use drugs. Streas, however, is a very normal part of life. It is important to understand that stress doesn't come from an event itself, that is, from the things that are happening in our lives. It comes from the meaning we give to what has happened. For example, a crying baby may be stressful to one person, but it may not bother another person at all, a traffic jam may be stressful to one person while another person may be able to stay calm. We can experience stress any time we...\n\nQ: According to the text,   _   can cause stress.", "options": ["overeat", "smoke", "a traffic jam", "a hard test."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 583, "question": "Dear Ms Morris, We have come to know of an unfortunate incident you had with our customer service department and we would like to deeply apologize for the inconvenience caused to you by the customer service manager's behavior. We have noted down your complaint (number 797329SA) and would like to let you know that strict action will be taken against the employee. He is a new employee with little experience and so his attitude towards his job was over enthusiastic and he lacked proper judgment. We are by no means excusing his behavior but I would like to request you not to take any legal action against the company as we are very sorry for what happened. To express our appreciation, please accept the offer of free servicing of all products of our company that you own for up to three years. We...\n\nQ: Why does David Johns mention their level of service in the past?", "options": ["To increase the service prices.", "To express thanks to the customer.", "To preserve the customer's confidence.", "To explain the causes of the poor service."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2682, "question": "Due to climate change, Arctic ice is breaking up earlier in the spring, and its area is decreasing. This is creating problems for polar bears that make their homes off northern Alaska and in Hudson Bay. Polar bears off Alaska normally hunt and raise their young on ice sheets that float on the ocean. But as the ice has melted, the polar bears have been forced to spend more time on land. There, they have begun to frequent beaches, feeding on the remains of whales caught by native hunters. For polar bears, this food is less nutritious than seals that they normally catch on ice sheets. The shrinking ice has also forced more polar bears into the ocean. In the past, they only had to swim short distances between ice sheets. But as the ice has shrunk, polar bears have been forced to swim longer an...\n\nQ: What is true of polar bears that are spending more time on land in Alaska?", "options": ["Their young are dying.", "Their diet is changing.", "Their health is improving.", "Their families are growing."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2509, "question": "A pair of pandas being lent by China to Japan was set to arrive in Tokyo's Ueno Zoo in the Japanese capital and raising hopes that the animals may help improve bilateral ties. Bi Li and his female partner, Xian Nu, both 5, were due to at Narita international Airport in Tokyo on a flight from Shanghai. Together with their keeper, the pair were transferred from Chengdu, to Shanghai on Monday morning, said Li Desheng, deputy chief of the Wolong Nature Reserve. The pair, which are young adults, will be the first pandas at Ueno Zoo since April 2008, when the institution's beloved Ling Ling died. Ueno Zoo had spent 90 million yen ($1.1 million) installing under-floor heating, a playground with a sandbox and landscaping. The pair will dine on rare bamboo from the central Japanese mountain of Izu ...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us    _    .", "options": ["a pair of pandas was lent to Japan by China", "the pair of pandas from China brought hope of improving Sino-Japanese relations", "the normalization of diplomatic ties between China and Japan", "sino-Japanese relations have been at a low point since the Diaoyu Island incident"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1990, "question": "Recently, South Korean star PSY's 'Gangnam style\" video has been popular on the Internet. It has become most people's favorite music. In fact, the song has set the Guinness World Record for the most popular video in the history of the Internet. More than two million people have said \"like\" since the song was on the Internet on July 15. PSY\"s special dance moves and funny horse riding style have attracted many people. Although many people do not understand the language, the video has become the talk of the Internet. The song has come to first place in the music charts in 31 countries, including the United States, the United Kingdom, and Canada. \"I just sang for my South Korean fans. I have never expected it to be popular in other countries,\" PSY told the reporters on a concert. The song was...\n\nQ: What's \"Gangnam Style\" about?", "options": ["The way of horse riding.", "The rich life of people of Gangnam in Seoul.", "The Guinness World Record.", "The love of stars."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1872, "question": "When people talk about Golden Age in Leadville, Horace Austin Warner Tabor and his second wife, Elizabeth McCourt must be included. Their story is becoming one of the legends of the Old West. H.A.W.Tabor was a school teacher in Vermont. With his first wife and two children he left Vermont in 1855 to settle in Kansas. Perhaps he was attracted by rumors of fortunes to be made in Colorado mines. A few years later he moved west to the small Colorado mining camp known as California Gulch, which he later renamed Leadville when he became its leading citizen. \"Great deposits of lead are sure to be found here.\"he said. As it turned out, it was silver, not lead, that was to make Leadville's fortune and wealth. Tabor knew little about mining himself, so he opened a general store selling everything fr...\n\nQ: According to the passage, why was Tabor able to achieve great success in Leadville?", "options": ["His wise decisions helped him achieve goals.", "He knew miners there were poor.", "He succeeded quite by accident.", "His second wife helped him a lot."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 224, "question": "Bob was born in Cambridge. When he was in elementary school, he asked his mother to take him to parks in their community so he could collect empty soda cans to recycle. His mother agreed, as long as he saved part of the money he earned for college. Bob's mother remembers Bob as the most determined of her seven kids. Bob's persistence paid off. On Friday, he will become the first person in his family, originally from El Salvador, to graduate from college. And he's graduating with university honors. For his honors thesis he researched unmanned solar-powered airplanes, which BYU students have been building and testing for about 10 years. Bob's study helps discover the best way to fly a solar-powered airplane so that it uses the least amount of power. The goal is to design and build an airplan...\n\nQ: It can be inferred that  _  .", "options": ["Bob's mother is in a way to becoming a dentist", "Bob's mother works in their community", "Bon's father will graduate from Utah Valley University on Friday", "Bob's father learnt to read at the age of 3"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2215, "question": "Picking up objects plays an important role in people's life. El-E is a robot that is designed to get everyday objects for people with disabilities. About 1.5 meters tall, with a single robotic arm that can pick up objects at different heights, El-E is equipped to discover what its owner wants and then go and fetch it. The user can point a location to the robot using a \"point-and-click\" way of interaction, which provides a direct way to tell the robot which object to handle or where to go. The robot can adapt the position of its arm in order to grasp the object. After successful early trials, some scientists expanded El-E's functions and tried to combine voice commands with the laser in order to do more complicated tasks, like opening doors. The robot recognizes words such as \"pull\" or \"pus...\n\nQ: How do Charlie and his colleagues develop El-E?", "options": ["By having it communicate with more people.", "By making it able to fetch more items.", "By letting it pick up objects more accurately.", "By getting it changeable at different occasions."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 361, "question": "Now that America has declared a state of swine flu public health emergency, you may be asking yourself -- what am Isupposed to do? Here is a list of practical steps you can take to prepare and protect yourself and your family. 1) Know the symptoms-- Here are some of the symptoms that sound like swine flu -- fevers over 100 degrees (37.8degC), body aches, cough, runny nose, and sometimes, nausea and diarrhea . It's also useful to know if you might have had an exposure either by recent travel to Mexico, or to the areas of known cases so far in America -- specific areas of California, Texas, New York, Ohio and Kansas. Or you may have been exposed to a sick person who came from those areas. 2) Don't panic-- If you have symptoms that sound like swine flu, do not rush to hospitals. Not only is t...\n\nQ: Suppose Mr Fernando has just been back from prefix = st1 /Mexicoand he's got a high fever and runny nose, what shall he do?", "options": ["Go to hospital as soon as possible.", "Ask a day off and stay at home.", "Call his doctor to ask for directions.", "Take some medicine and have a good rest."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2498, "question": "Have you ever wanted to feel like you were in a western film? Or maybe you wanted to feel like you were a pioneer traveling the west? It is possible to experience such things during a Wild West vacation! Here are four of the best Wild West vacation locations available: Walk the Lewis and Clark Trail Walk some or all of the 3,700 miles trail that was traversed by Mariwether Lewis and William Clark, two of the world's greatest explorers. Though not all the trails are marked, there are various stops that have been preserved by various historic societies. There is also a coach that makes a 16-day _ following the trail. This begins in St. Louis, Missouri, and ends in Astoria, Oregon. Venture Route 66 Take a tour or go to see it yourself -- ride on the famous Route 66. The road is nearly 2,500 m...\n\nQ: If you want to hike various trails you are advised to  _  .", "options": ["visit the Grand Canyon", "visit Deadwood", "venture Route 66", "walk the Lewis and Clark Trail"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2902, "question": "Remember that goals are dreams with a timetable. Our goals are important for us to create what enriches our life. A very common attitude among people who are successful is that their success lies in their ability to provide themselves goals that are both numerous and exciting. When you think about your future,you are helping to feed a long-term goal of what you want to create. To realize your dreams,you must translate your vision into a series of actions you can take as soon as possible. You should be able to measure these results,to make sure they take you wherever you want. And this step should not be viewed lightly! Indeed,very few people set goals and concrete actions for themselves to achieve. Very few people note what they want to accomplish,and know each day whether they have indeed...\n\nQ: If you put down your goals on the paper,you can  _  .", "options": ["know clearly what should be done", "make them accomplished smoothly", "measure the results of the goals easily", "mention them easily to others"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2596, "question": "Parties held by the wealthy seldom welcome poor guests.But last week China made it through the doors into a gathering of the world's richest countries. Jin Renqing ,Chian's finance minister,and Zhou Xiaochuan,governor of the People's Bank of China,joined a meeting of the Group of Seven(G7)on October1,2004.It is the fist time that China has had direct talks with the club.It was a good chance to share the world powers'thoughts about critical economic issues and _ understanding. China'a participation is a natural part of its increasingly important role in the global economy.China is the world 's factory and the biggest market. America and China made up almost half of global economic growth last year.\"If Anerican consumers and Chinese producers were to reduce their activities at the same time,...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true?", "options": ["China's participation in the meeting of G7 is the first time that China has talks with the developed countries.", "The stable economy of China has done a great deal to the development of the world.", "The developed nations are trying their best to help the poorer countries at present", "America has as large a market as China has."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 298, "question": "Since we are social beings, the quality of our lives depends in large measure on our interpersonal relationships.One strength of the human condition is our tendency to give and receive support from one another under stressful circumstances.Social support consists of the exchange of resources among people based on their interpersonal ties.Those of us with strong support systems appear better able to deal with major life changes and daily difficulties.People with strong social ties live longer and have better health than those without such ties.Studies over a range of illnesses, from depression to heart disease, show that the presence of social support helps people protect themselves from illness, and the absence of such support makes poor health more likely. Social support _ stress in a num...\n\nQ: Social companionship is beneficial in that it", "options": ["helps strengthen our ties with relatives", "enables us to get rid of our faults and mistakes", "makes our leisure time activities more enjoyable", "draws our attention away from our worries and troubles"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 651, "question": "Lee Ann Laraway has polio and is not able to move very much. Most things are out of reach for her. Jeannie, a Labrador retriever, acts as her arms and legs. Jeannie understands 72 or more different commands. On a shopping trip, she can get money for Lee Ann at the bank or candies at the store. She can pay the cashier and get change back. Jeannie brings things to Lee Ann and puts them in her lap. Jeannie was trained at a place called Canine Companions for Independence, located on twelve acres of land in Santa Rosa (California). The land was donated by the cartoonist Charles Shultz. \"We train four different types of dogs here,\" said Ken Kirsh, a dog trainer there. \"Hearing dogs, service dogs, skilled companion dogs, and facility dogs.\" Trainers work with Labrador retrievers and golden retrie...\n\nQ: Jeannie can help Lee Ann do all the following things EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["go to the bank to get money", "pay for what Lee Ann buys in the shop", "bring things home", "do some cooking at home"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1985, "question": "Shakespeare's Sister Let us imagine, since facts are so hard to come by, what would have happened had Shakespeare had a wonderfully gifted sister, called Judith. Shakespeare himself went, very probably -- his mother was an heiress -- to the grammar school, where he may have learnt Latin -- Ovid, Virgil and Horace -- and the elements of grammar and logic. He was, it is well known, a wild boy who poached rabbits, perhaps shot a deer, and had, rather sooner than he should have done, to marry a woman in the neighborhood, who bore him a child rather quicker than was right. That escapade sent him to seek his fortune in London. He had, it seemed, a taste for the theatre; he began by holding horses at the stage door. Very soon he got work in the theatre, became a successful actor, and lived at the...\n\nQ: What can we infer from Judith's teen life?", "options": ["She was cared for but was expected to live a girl's life.", "She was willing to be engaged to a wool stapler.", "Her father wanted to make a fortune by her marriage.", "She got less affection from her parents than her brother."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2829, "question": "Are you the kind of person who likes staying in unusual places? If the answer is \"yes\", then try the world's coldest hotel in Jukkasjarvi in the north of Sweden. But go in winter to all you'll find is a pool of water, because the hotel melts every spring! The man who runs the Artic Hall Hotel is Nils Yngve Bergqvist. He built his first ice building for an art exhibition in 1991 and he designed the present hotel-over 200 meters square-himself. It took workmen about two months to pile 1,000 tons of snow onto a wooden base. As the weather got colder, the snow froze and then they removed the base. The whole building and everything in it are made of snow-except for the wooden front door. There's a theatre which Nils uses for a jazz club, a radio station and a large ice bar. As you can imagine, ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is probably the best title?", "options": ["Staying in Unusual Places", "The Unusual Hotel", "Ice Hotel-Cold Comfort", "The Hall Exhibition"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1767, "question": "Dear Cassy, Thanks for reminding me by e-mail that you want to baby-sit our children. In spite of the fact that you are only 15 years old, my wife and I would be willing to consider your application if you can meet a few modest requirements: 1. three letters from teachers who will prove that you have never failed to follow directions perfectly in class and never failed to hand in the homework on time. 2. Submit a note from two doctors which says that you are in perfect health, have never been sick, and will never be sick. 3. Submit a document from your physical education teacher or team coach that proves that you can do each of the following: Run two miles in less than nine minutes, climb an oily rope to a height of twenty feet in thirty seconds while balancing a glass of water on your nos...\n\nQ: What can we infer from this text?", "options": ["Their children are hard to baby-sit.", "Their children are well educated.", "Cassy is good at doing many things.", "Cassy won't get the job as a baby-sitter."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 79, "question": "What's your idea of a good time? What about dancing in a rainy field with one hundred and fifty thousand other people while a famous rock band plays on a stage so far away that the performers look like ants? It may sound strange but that is what many hundreds of thousands of young people in the UK do every summer.Why? Because summer is the time for outdoor music festivals. Held on a farm, the Glastonbury Festival is the most well-known and popular festival in the UK.It began in 1970 and the first festival was attended by one thousand five hundred people each paying an admission price of PS1 -- the ticket included free milk from the farm. Since then the Glastonbury Festival has gone from strength to strength -- in 2004 one hundred and fifty thousand fans attended, paying PS112 each for a ti...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["How to have a good time", "Charity events around the world", "The Glastonbury Festival", "Superstars' performances in charity events"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1595, "question": "Narasimha Das is on his way to feed 169,379 hungry children. Das is in charge of a kitchen in Vrindaban. The town is about a three-hour drive from India's capital, New Delhi. Das gets to work at 3:00 a.m. Thirty workers are already working to make tens of thousands of rounds of bread. It will be brought to 1,516 schools in and around Vrindaban. A Growing Problem Going to school is difficult for more than 13 million children in India. They must go to work instead, or go hungry. That's why India began the Mid-Day Meal Scheme, the largest school-lunch program in the world. A free lunch encourages children to come to school and gives them the energy they need for learning. The program began in the 1960s. The kitchen in Vrindaban is run by the Akshaya Patra Foundation. It is one of the lunch pr...\n\nQ: Why is it difficult for children to go to school in India?", "options": ["Because there are not enough teachers.", "Because there are not enough schools.", "Because they have to work to make money.", "Because their parents refuse to send them to school."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2923, "question": "British MPs have voted in favour of the creation of babies with DNA from two women and one man, in a historic move. The UK is now set to become the first country to introduce laws to allow the creation of babies from three people. In a free vote in the Commons, 382 MPs were in favour and 128 against the technique that stops genetic diseases being passed from mother to child. During the debate, ministers said the technique was \"light at the end of a dark tunnel\" for families. A further vote is required in the House of Lords. If everything goes ahead then the first such baby could be born next year. Supporters said it was \"good news for progressive medicine\" but critics say they will continue to fight against the technique that they say raises too many ethical and safety concerns. Estimates ...\n\nQ: Prime Minister David Cameron   _   the creation of such babies.", "options": ["is in favour of", "throws doubt on", "objects to", "is indifferent to"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2947, "question": "Animals can be extremely protective of their young. But when hard times call, animal fathers can be really a danger to their own kids. Daddy Lion A combination of laziness, pride, cruelty and anger makes the lion one of the most fearsome and worst dads of the animal kingdom. When not walking proudly across the jungle, the father lion just lazes around under the sun, or waits for one of its lioness partners to bring back food. Once the lioness gets home the food, the lion eats up most of it, and leaves little or nothing at all for the kids. The father doesn't even train the kids for hunting and surviving, it is the lioness who teaches them how to _ themselves. The Polar Father Cute, pure and soft. Protective of young ones and family? Sure. But what makes the polar bears one of the worst dad...\n\nQ: The animal fathers mentioned in this article   _  .", "options": ["are protective of their young", "are respected by their young", "are rather bad to their kids", "are dangerous to their whole family"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2907, "question": "Pulling heavy suitcases all day in the summer is hard work, especially when you are a thin 14-year-old boy. That was me in 1940-the youngest and smallest baggage boy at New York City's Pennsylvania Railway Station. After just a few days on the job, I began noticing that the other fellows were overcharging passengers. I'd like to join them, thinking, \"Everyone else is doing it.\" When I got home that night, I told my dad what I wanted to do. \"You give an honest day's work,\" he said, looking at me straight in his eye. \"They are paying you. If they want to do that, you let them do that.\" I followed my dad's advice for the rest of that summer and have lived by his words ever since. Of all the jobs I've had, it was my experience at Pennsylvania Railway Station that has stuck with me. Now I teach...\n\nQ: It can be concluded from the text that   _", "options": ["his father's advice helped him to decide which job to take up", "working in the sports team was his most important experience", "he learned much from his shared experience with his team members", "his experience as a baggage boy had a great influence on his late life"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3266, "question": "If you are ever planning to buy a telescope and want to get yourself involved in astronomy it is always a good idea to know a bit of the sky.Get acquainted with a few constellations so that it will be easier for you to spot the constellations when you are using your telescope. It's a good idea to buy a few magazines on astronomy to help you to get familiar with the constellations in the sky and also read a few reviews on the different types of telescopes in the market.This will help you gather all the information that is out there regarding telescopes and what people have to say about them. It's advisable to go in for a pair of binoculars before you buy your first telescope so that you can get used to spotting constellations before your view of the sky is narrowed down.This will also help ...\n\nQ: According to the text,a telescope is intended to be bought for   _  .", "options": ["getting experience", "watching stars", "studying the climate", "learning about a bit of the sky"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1842, "question": "One rainy night , Mark decided to end his life . Having undergone a lot of sufferings and frustrations , he walked the streets , feeling desperate . On that same night , I was sitting in my room when I heard the doorbell rang . My mom opened the door , finding herself face-to-face with a very disheveled-looking man , Mark , with tears running down his face . My mom , overcome by pity , invited him inside . Curious , I went downstairs to get a better look . The sight of the man , holding his head in his hands and crying , made my chest ache . I raced back upstairs to my room , pulled out my only half-dollar coin from my money jar and ran back downstairs . When I reached the door of the living room , I walked right in and quickly made my way over to the stranger . I put the half-dollar in hi...\n\nQ: What can be the best title for the passage ?", "options": ["Love is Selfless", "Kindness is Rewarding", "Love Saves All", "Be Kind to Strangers"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2971, "question": "My father, at the death of his father, was six years old, and he grew up without education. He moved from Kentucky to Indiana when I was seven. We reached our new home about the time the state came into the Union. It was a wild area, with many bears and other wild animals still in the woods. I grew up there. There were some so-called schools, but what was required of a teacher never went beyond \"reading, writing, and adding.\" If a stranger supposed to understand Latin happened to live for a time in the area, he was looked on as wizard . There was simply nothing to excite a desire for education. Of course, when I grew up, I did not know much. Still, somehow, I could read, write, and add, but that was all. The advance I have now made is on this store of education, which I have picked up unde...\n\nQ: When the writer was seven, his family moved to an area where   _  .", "options": ["educated people were greatly respected", "only a few had a knowledge of Latin", "people were often killed by wild animals", "the land had yet to be farmed"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2251, "question": "France is one of the largest countries in Europe. It is bordered by six countries -- Belgium, Luxembourg and Germany to the north-east, Switzerland and Italy across the Alps to the south-east and Spain across the Pyrenees to the south-west. The UK is across the English Channel. France has several large international airports, two of which are in the capital, Paris. Visitors from the UK also can take the Channel Tunnel rail link down to France. In France, the highway network and French rail service are known to be extremely efficient with the high-speed, and they become the envy of other nations. France is the world's most popular tourist destination . The country has an extremely beautiful scene and an equally comfortable climate to match. This makes it suitable for a huge range of excitin...\n\nQ: What do people in other countries think of Frenchmen according to the passage?", "options": ["Rich.", "Proud.", "Polite.", "Rude."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1929, "question": "Most people believe they don't have imagination. They are wrong. Everyone has imagination, but most of us,once we became adults, forget how to access it. Creativity isn't always connected with great works of art or ideas. People at work and in their free time routinely think of creative ways to solve problems. Maybe you have a goal to achieve,a tricky question to answer or you just want to expand your mind! Here are three techniques to help you. This technique involves taking unrelated ideas and trying to find links between them. First,think about the problem you have to solve or the job you need to do. Then find an image,word,idea or object,for example,a candle. Write down all the ideas/words associated with candles:light,fire,matches, wax,night,silence,etc. Think of as many as you can. T...\n\nQ: According to the passage, when we become adults,   _   .", "options": ["most of us are no longer creative", "we can still learn to be more creative", "we are not as imaginative as children", "we are unwilling to be creative"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1033, "question": "I was now in my twenty third year of residence in this island and was accustomed to the place and to the manner of living. If it had not been the savages who had come to the place to disturb me, I could have been content to spent the rest of my time there, even to the last moment, till I had laid me down and died, like the old goat in the cave. I had also arrived to some little recreations and amusements, which made the time pass more pleasantly with me a great deal than it did before. At first, I had taught my Poll to speak. And he did it so familiarly and talked so clearly and plain that it was very pleasant to me. And he lived with me no less than twenty six years. How long he might live afterwards, I don't know; though I know they have an idea in Brazil that they live a hundred years. ...\n\nQ: What does the passage mainly talk about?", "options": ["Robin Crusoe treated animals kindly.", "Robin Crusoe led a hard life on the island.", "The animals raised by Robin Crusoe brought him much pleasure.", "The savages always spoiled Robin Crusoe's happy life."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2464, "question": "For a long time now, I've been fascinated by common phrases and their origins- and just why we say what we say. I decided to consult the experts, sort through all the research and compile the answers. Here are a few of the standouts. Q: Why do we\"tie the knot \"when we get married? A: Knots have been a common metaphor in marriage ceremonies all over the world and through time. The expression means\"to unite in manage\". In the Hindu marriage ceremony, the groom ties a ribbon around the bride's neck. In ancient Rome, the bride wore a belt that was tied in a knot. The groom would then unfasten it on their first night together as husband and wife. Q: Why do we say\"Many happy returns\"? A: The phrase is short for\"Many happy returns of the day\", which is to say,\"May this day return many times\"or\"Ma...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following phrases is related to the sea?", "options": ["Tie the knot.", "Many happy returns.", "It's not over till the fat lady sings.", "Under the weather."], "answer": 3}]